PERSONAL INFORMATION

• Evan Lin 林仰行

• Phone: +886 980 811 084

• Email: yanghsin.lin@gmail.com

• LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/proevan

• Github: https://github.com/proevan

I have been a software developer for four years specializing in Android app, website and API development. And most familiar with Android app and 3rd party library development, very interested in UI&UX and Unit Testing and UI Testing in Android, also doing some front-end and back-end works using Java, Kotlin, JSP, Struts, RESTful API, Python, Shell Script etc..

EDUCATION

- Android Developer Nanodegree, Udacity 2015 2016
- Bachelor of Computer Science, National Taiwan University of Science and Technology 2006 – 2010

WORK EXPERIENCE

Loopd Inc. (2014/11 - now)

Loopd is a startup company focusing on providing IOT and data analytics solutions for event industry.

- The only person who is responsible for building Android apps and writing Unit&UI testings
- Made SDK of Loopd Bluetooth devices
- Technics Applied: Android Studio, Material Design, Parse, BLE, iBeacon, Twitter SDK, Realm, Pubnub, Retrofit, Dagger2, Mockito, Espresso, Shell Script, Unit Testing, UI Testing, TDD, Scrum, Kotlin, RxJava, Reactive Programming, MVP, Mosby, Clean Architecture

WayStorm Co. Ltd. (2012/5 - 2014/10)

KuAd (WSAd)

KuAd is one of the biggest localized mobile advertising network in Taiwan. I restructure and rebuild a new version SDK for Android platform independently, and

also join the team to restructure and make new type of advertising for improving user advertising experience.

- Rewroted Android SDK with new architecture independently.
- Redesigned the client-server communication architecture.
- Made SDK more stable, efficient and easy to integrate.
- In charge of maintaining, updating new feature and documentation for Android SDK.
- Technics Applied: Java, Android, MVC, Proguard, MRAID, Google Analytics, Admob, RESTful API

Breeze

Breezecenter is a well-known department store in Taiwan. This is a outsourcing project from Breeze Inc. including official website(including management site), Android app, iOS app and some customized service. I'm a fullstack developer in this project.

- Implemented and maintained the official Android app independently
- Implemented the official website and also the backend management site
- 3 team members in this project.
- Technics Applied: Java, JSP, Struts, Spring, Hibernate, MySQL, Jenkins, RESTful API, JavaScript, CSS, Linux

Taiwan district map

In order to get district of addresses from latitude and longitude, I generated the Taiwan district map in 2-dimensional matrix.

- Generated the Taiwan district map(2030x3500) using less than 1000 times Google Map API
- 1 team member for this project and completed in 7 days.
- Technics Applied: Python, Google Map API, Shell Script

VieshowFunMovie

Implemented a Windows Phone app for Vieshow Cinemas. Cooperated with Microsoft and gave a demo at Windows phone promotion event at Taipei.

- 1 team member for this project
- Technics Applied: Windows Phone 7, C#

Self-Employed

Monster Strike Game Guide

Official licensed Android game guide app for Monster Strike

• Technics Applied: Java, Android

SightsDoor

Outsourcing project from a Japan company. Implemented the Android app.

- Cooperated and had been a mobile side technical consultant for 3 months.
- Technics Applied: Java, Android, Facebook Android SDK, RESTful API, JSON, Git

Paradise

A private customized service. Sign in and crawl data from websites. Send notifications and display the data in app.

- 2 team members for this project
- Technics Applied: Java, Android, MySQL, SWT, Jsoup, RESTful API, JSON, Git, Parse, OpenShift